Hey Matt,
we're good at if it goes if Philly
doesn't pick we're good at
Chargers for
for 131 and 202.
Here's Ali and Wolf.
Gabe, what's up man?
Congratulations man. Pick it here.
Welcome to New England.
Yeah man, thank you for the opportunity.
We're excited. All right, here's coach
Vrabel.
Gabe.
Hey buddy, congratulations man. I'm so
proud proud of you. I'm so happy for
you.
Hey, thank you man. Thank so You are
everything that we are about man. You
came into our building on that visit and
not one person
when you left here everybody was like we
got to find a way to get this guy on our
football team.
I'm going to give you to our owner Mr.
Kraft and he wants to welcome you onto
our football team.
Gabe.
Gabe. How you doing?
Congrats man.
Thank you. You're a little emotional
I know I'm I'm I'm I'm emotional man.
Thank you so much. Thank you for Thank
you for giving me the opportunity y'all.
I'm
I promise I'm going to give you
everything I got. Day one I promise you.
I appreciate that. That's really nice.
Good job boys.
>> [applause]